Have some water.
How are you feeling?
A bit better.
Okay.
Make sure you get some rest these next few days.
Daddy!
What are you doing here?
Yixin.
Come here.
You two know each other?
Of course, she's my...
sister.
Sister?
She's met me twice,
and both times called me Daddy.
Besides,
the name Yixin...
Is she really your sister?
Yes.
You were locked up for four years.
Is it that strange I have a three-year-old sister?
Kids don't know any better, so they just call people whatever.
Yixin, you can't call him that anymore.
Understand?
He's not your daddy.
Okay.
Director Ren, are you making rounds or...?
I'm not the director anymore.
Well, if you're fine,
then I'll head back.
Yixin.
Have you really met him twice?
Yes.
The first time, Daddy picked up my ball.
The second time, Junjun bullied me,
and Daddy saved me.
Daddy's so amazing!
He knocked down Junjun's dad in one go.
Daddy is obviously Daddy.
Why won't Ruo Jin let me call him Daddy?
Inmate Ren Feifan has refused this visit.
You can write or book another visit.
But he'll have to agree.
He still won't forgive me?
The inmate still refuses to see you.
Why did Mommy say she's my sister?
Aren't sisters younger than moms?
Why are you following me?
I saw you at Premier Medical Hall and the hospital.
Good memory.
Hi, I'm Su Qing.
A reporter for Beishi Daily.
Answer my question.
I was investigating something.
I thought it involved you.
But then I realized...
it didn't.
Then why are you still following me?
Don't let the family near the body.
One quick look from afar at the hospital morgue,
then rush it to the funeral home.
Remember, keep the family away from the body.
One quick look from afar, then off to the funeral home.
That's Li Xiande.
Yes.
A year ago, a patient's family came to me.
Said his son died during Li Xiande's emergency care.
He wanted answers from the hospital,
but was blocked from all sides,
pressured to drop it.
First they offered him a fortune,
then came the violent threats.
The Wang Family did it.
So...
you also think they're illegally trafficking organs?
Where are you going?
To examine the body.
Yesterday, Li Xiande had a patient who died during emergency care.
What's his name?
Wang Dong.
He's right here.
Why aren't there any signs of him being cut open
to have his organs removed?
Give me a hand.
What is this?
Drug residue. Highly toxic.
You mean he was poisoned to death?
Shh.
Are you okay?
You're soaked.
Let's go.
Good thing I just misheard.
Noises in the middle of the night are terrifying.
Let's go.
Dazhuang.
Put this on first.
Here.
Master.
What's going on here?
Don't get the wrong idea.
This is Su Qing, a reporter for Beishi Daily.
Hello, nice to meet you.
What's the situation inside?
Based on my prior investigation,
there should be an experimental base inside this hospital.
I suspect they're using ER patients
for human experimentation.
That's outrageous!
Actually experimenting on human beings!
You're saying this hospital isn't trafficking organs,
but conducting some kind of experiment?
Yeah.
Truly, hell is empty,
and all the devils are here.
How are things between you two lately?
Last time we went to Lijia Village together,
I feel like he
seems to
still be interested in you.
I don't know if he's interested.
That hurts!
How boring.
What's your relationship with Ren Feifan?
We're just colleagues.
What about you?
What's your relationship with him?
I...
Let me tell you,
Ren Feifan has a wife and child.
You'd better not keep hanging around him...
Sorry about that.
She's got the wrong person.
She's an obsessed fan of Dr. Ren's.
Seems like she didn't get the wrong person.
And who exactly are you?
Me?
Who am I?
Stop asking.
Just stop asking.
Please stop asking.
Calm down.
Let's go, let's go.
Lunatics.
The most likely place is right here.
Dazhuang,
this time you'll pose as a myocarditis patient.
I'll apply needles to seal your meridians.
You'll feel dizzy,
and anemia will leave your limbs weak and face pale.
Remember, don't get worked up.
Breathe slowly.
No problem.
Remember, whether we succeed or not,
you must ensure your own safety.
Our goal this time is to scout the way.
Once you find the main gate, come right back.
Got it?
Got it.
And take this.
What's this?
It's a hidden camera.
Blink twice and it starts recording.
Close your eyes for over 30 seconds to turn it off.
Understood?
Understood.
Let's do this, Master.